WENDY KOBAYASHI

Email: wykobayashi@gmail.com | Phone: 949-351-1008 | Lake Forest, CA

LinkedIn: https://bit.ly/3wcC13C | GitHub: https://bit.ly/2QPcSO7 | Portfolio: https://bit.ly/3h5F1en

CAREER SUMMARY

Motivated Full Stack Web Developer with 4+ years as a regulatory professional and 6+ years as an engineer in the medical device industry. Strengths include strong organizational and planning skills, ability to problem-solve and make sound decisions, and collaborating in a team environment.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap/Materialize, Handlebars, Responsive Design, RESTful APIs, Git/GitHub, Heroku, Node.js, Express, User Authentication, MySQL, MongoDB

PROJECTS

Pet Connect | Co-Developer | GitHub: https://bit.ly/3ythRUn | Deployed: https://bit.ly/3dAodtq

- A social media application that is designed to connect pet owners through posts and comments.
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Handlebars, Node.js, Bcrypt, Dotenv, Express, Session, MySQL, Nodemailer, Sequelize, Heroku, Insomnia

Tech Blog | Developer | GitHub: https://bit.ly/2V2wTlY | Deployed: https://bit.ly/3yhUTjd

- A blog site that can be used to publish blog posts and comment on other users' posts.
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Handlebars, Node.js, Bcrypt, Dotenv, Express, Session, MySQL, Sequelize, Heroku, Insomnia

Make It / Buy It | Co-Developer | GitHub: https://bit.ly/3jrxWpm | Deployed: https://bit.ly/3kusnr1

- A web application that retrieves recipes and restaurants based on user input.
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Materialize, Spoonacular API, Yelp API

WORK EXPERIENCE

Applied Medical - Rancho Santa Margarita, CA

Apr 2010 to Present

Director, Regulatory Affairs | Dec 2016 to Present

- Managed the Post-Market Regulatory Affairs team (31 team members).
- Reduced the backlog of complaints by 75%.
- Led the implementation of new software, which improved the timeliness of the complaints by 25%.

Director, Engineering | May 2015 to Dec 2016

• Provided guidance and assisted with the development of a device, which involved collaborating with other teams to define the project scope, identify requirements, and develop specifications.

Manager, Engineering | Jan 2013 to May 2015

 Created project plans to track deliverables and identify critical tasks, which ensured that project milestones were met.

Engineer | Apr 2010 to Jan 2013

Completed improvement projects to increase the efficiency of manufacturing processes.

EDUCATION

University of California, Irvine Division of Continuing Education, CA

Aug 2021

Certificate, Full Stack Web Development

University of California, Irvine, CA

Mar 2010

Bachelor of Science, Mechanical Engineering